(Leonard:)We're here to see Koothrappali,
not kill Batman.
(Howard:)Try less teeth.
(Leonard:)Close enough. Come on.
- Hey, Raj.
- Hey, guys. What's up?
We wanted to invite you
out to dinner tonight.
Celebrate your 30 Under 30 thing.
Right, Sheldon?
- It's very nice of you. I would like that.
- Hello, boys.
- Dr. Gablehauser.
- Dr. Koothrappali.
- Dr. Hofstadter.
- Dr. Gablehauser.
- Dr. Cooper.
- Mr. Wolowitz.
Boys, I got a question for you.
Who in this room discovered a star?
Actually, 2008-NQ sub-17
is a planetary body.
(Gablehauser:)I'm not talking about you,
I'm talking about me.
(Gablehauser:)You, my exotic young friend, are my star.
But you didn't discover him.
You merely noticed he was here...
...much like he did with 2008-NQ sub-17.